[
    {
        "question": "What is the highest mountain in England? ",
        "correct": "Scafell Pike",
        "wrong1": "Snowdon",
        "wrong2": "Kinderscout",
        "wrong3": "Ben Nevis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Every year Oxford take on Cambridge in which famous event in London?",
        "correct": "Boat Race",
        "wrong1": "Rubber Duck Race",
        "wrong2": "Rugby",
        "wrong3": "Tug of war"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word follows Holland, Green and Wembley to complete the name of three London tube stations? ",
        "correct": "Park",
        "wrong1": "Gardens",
        "wrong2": "Center",
        "wrong3": "Street"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which English singer had hits with Set Fire To The Rain and Rolling In The Deep?",
        "correct": "Adele",
        "wrong1": "Lord",
        "wrong2": "Ed Sheeran",
        "wrong3": "Ariana Grande"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do Nyetimber and Rathfinny produce? ",
        "correct": "Wine",
        "wrong1": "Timber",
        "wrong2": "Clocks",
        "wrong3": "Bedsheets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Truro is the most southerly city in mainland England, but in which county is it located? ",
        "correct": "Cornwall",
        "wrong1": "Devin",
        "wrong2": "Hampshire",
        "wrong3": "Kent"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city would you walk down 'The Shambles'?",
        "correct": "York",
        "wrong1": "London",
        "wrong2": "Chester",
        "wrong3": "Manchester"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is traditionally rolled down Cooperâ€™s Hill in Gloucestershire, and then is raced after by locals?",
        "correct": "Cheese",
        "wrong1": "Children",
        "wrong2": "Raffas",
        "wrong3": "Conkers"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Serpentine is a body of water found in which park in England? ",
        "correct": "Hyde Park",
        "wrong1": "St James Park",
        "wrong2": "Green Park",
        "wrong3": "Clapham Common"
    },
    {
        "question": "Durdle Door and Corfe Castle are located in which county? ",
        "correct": "Dorset",
        "wrong1": "Cornwall",
        "wrong2": "Devin",
        "wrong3": "Kent"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tamworth, Berkshire and Oxford Sandy and Black are breeds of which animal?",
        "correct": "Pig",
        "wrong1": "Dog",
        "wrong2": "Sheep",
        "wrong3": "Cow"
    },
    {
        "question": "By which major English city do you find the Clifton Suspension Bridge?",
        "correct": "Bristol",
        "wrong1": "Clifton",
        "wrong2": "London",
        "wrong3": "Birmingham"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city has more miles of canals than Venice?",
        "correct": "Birmingham",
        "wrong1": "London",
        "wrong2": "Oxford",
        "wrong3": "Cornwall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest lake in England?",
        "correct": "Lake Windermere",
        "wrong1": "Lake Bassenthwaite",
        "wrong2": "Lake Basalt",
        "wrong3": "Lake Derwent Water"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did London last host the Olympic games?",
        "correct": "2012",
        "wrong1": "2016",
        "wrong2": "2004",
        "wrong3": "2020"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Big Tower near Parlament is usually referred to by what common name?",
        "correct": "St Stephen's Tower",
        "wrong1": "The Clock Tower",
        "wrong2": "Big Ben",
        "wrong3": "Queens Watchtower"
    },
    {
        "question": "'You kiss by the book' is a line from which Shakespeare play?",
        "correct": "Romeo and Juliet",
        "wrong1": "Hamlet",
        "wrong2": "Much to do about nothing",
        "wrong3": "Macbeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which English pudding has layers of jam, frangipane, and a topping of flaked almonds, on a shortcrust pastry base?",
        "correct": "Bakewell Tart",
        "wrong1": "Yorkshire Pie",
        "wrong2": "Cranberry Slice",
        "wrong3": "The Scots are coming!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second-largest city in England?",
        "correct": "Birmingham",
        "wrong1": "London",
        "wrong2": "Bristol",
        "wrong3": "Oxford"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the patron saint of England?",
        "correct": "St George",
        "wrong1": "St James",
        "wrong2": "St Andrews",
        "wrong3": "St Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tallest building in England?",
        "correct": "The Shard",
        "wrong1": "The Pike",
        "wrong2": "The Gerkin",
        "wrong3": "The Sky Tower"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official animal of England?",
        "correct": "Lion",
        "wrong1": "Dragon",
        "wrong2": "Unicorn",
        "wrong3": "Eagle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the slang word given to the London Underground?",
        "correct": "The Tube",
        "wrong1": "Under",
        "wrong2": "Downtown",
        "wrong3": "The Metro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour is the packaging of a Cadbury Dairy Milk bar?",
        "correct": "Purple",
        "wrong1": "Blue",
        "wrong2": "White",
        "wrong3": "Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fish is traditionally used to make fish and chips?",
        "correct": "Cod",
        "wrong1": "Trout",
        "wrong2": "Salmon",
        "wrong3": "Herring"
    },
    {
        "question": "How far is England from France?",
        "correct": "32 km",
        "wrong1": "30 km",
        "wrong2": "28 km",
        "wrong3": "26 km"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these famous scientists and inventors was not born in England?",
        "correct": "Alexander Graham Bell",
        "wrong1": "Isaac Newton",
        "wrong2": "Charles Darwin",
        "wrong3": "Stephen Hawkins"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Great British Bake Off start?",
        "correct": "2010",
        "wrong1": "2005",
        "wrong2": "2015",
        "wrong3": "2020"
    },
    {
        "question": "What wouldn't you find in a Full English Breakfast?",
        "correct": "Haddock",
        "wrong1": "Black Pudding",
        "wrong2": "Mushrooms",
        "wrong3": "Baked Beans"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many cups of tea do the British drink each day?",
        "correct": "100 million",
        "wrong1": "50 million",
        "wrong2": "10 million",
        "wrong3": "500 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Henry VIII's first wife?",
        "correct": "Catherine of Aragon",
        "wrong1": "Anne Boleyn",
        "wrong2": "Jane Seymour",
        "wrong3": "Anne of Cleves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of the following English monarchs reigned first?",
        "correct": "William IV",
        "wrong1": "George V",
        "wrong2": "Victoria",
        "wrong3": "Edward VII"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which scientist wrote 'The Theory of Everything'?",
        "correct": "Stephen Hawking",
        "wrong1": "Charles Darwin",
        "wrong2": "Rosalind Franklin",
        "wrong3": "Tim Berners-Lee"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the most visited museum in England in 2020?",
        "correct": "Tate Modern",
        "wrong1": "British Museum",
        "wrong2": "Natural History Museum",
        "wrong3": "Victoria and Albert Museum"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Glastonbury festival start?",
        "correct": "1970",
        "wrong1": "1960",
        "wrong2": "1980",
        "wrong3": "1990"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Prime Minister during the Brexit Referendum?",
        "correct": "David Cameron",
        "wrong1": "Theresa May",
        "wrong2": "Boris Johnson",
        "wrong3": "Liz Truss"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which cross is on the flag of England?",
        "correct": "Cross of St George",
        "wrong1": "Cross of the British Empire",
        "wrong2": "Cross of St Joseph",
        "wrong3": "Cross of the British Monarchy"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city can you hear a Cockney accent?",
        "correct": "London",
        "wrong1": "Liverpool",
        "wrong2": "Bristol",
        "wrong3": "Nottingham"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest river flowing entirely in England?",
        "correct": "Thames",
        "wrong1": "Severn",
        "wrong2": "Trent",
        "wrong3": "Tyne"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Adele's first album?",
        "correct": "19",
        "wrong1": "21",
        "wrong2": "20",
        "wrong3": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Prince Andrew's first wife?",
        "correct": "Sarah Ferguson",
        "wrong1": "Eugenie Brooksbank",
        "wrong2": "Ghislaine Maxwell",
        "wrong3": "Anne Tindall"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which county is Leeds?",
        "correct": "West Yorkshire",
        "wrong1": "Cambridgeshire",
        "wrong2": "Derbyshire",
        "wrong3": "East Sussex"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which National park can you find a mountain called Mam Tor?",
        "correct": "Peak District",
        "wrong1": "Lake District",
        "wrong2": "Yorkshire Dales",
        "wrong3": "Pembrokes Coast"
    }
]